# Sae Inoue

A fast learner who works well both independently and as part of a team. Serve coffee with 3 years of experience in food handling and high-quality customer service skills. Experienced in washing, keepinginventory stoked and ensuring the cleanliness of bar counters and utensils.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### All rounder

Splitting beans, Australia (Feb 2023 – August 2023)

- Took coffee, food, and other beverage orders and prepared them for customers quickly and effectively.
- Ensured the proper preparation of ingredients for meals.
- Provided a high level of customer service, speedily delivered meals and processed payments.
- Cleaned espresso machine and kitchen equipment to a high standard.
- Washed dishes and restocked the bar line for continued fast service capabilities.
- Assisted customers with sales transactions accurately and efficiently, including cash, check, card and layaway payments.

## Cashier, Waitress

Hifumiya Noodle Restaurant, Australia (Jan 2023- Fub 2023)

- Assisted in taking care of customers at the front desk who did not know what they wanted
- Responsible for keeping the floor clean.
- Stocked napkins, tea bags, silverware, and other supplies.
- Washed dishes and restocked the bar line for continued fast service capabilities
- Assisted customers with sales transactions accurately and efficiently, including cash, check, card and layaway payments

# Barista, Cashier

DEAN&DELUCA, Japan (Mar 2020 – Oct 2022)

- Took coffee, food, and other beverage orders and prepared them for customers quickly and effectively
- Ensured the proper preparation of ingredients for meals
- Provided a high level of customer service, speedily delivered meals and processed payments
- Cleaned espresso machine and kitchen equipment to a high standard
- Washed dishes and restocked the bar line for continued fast service capabilities
- Assisted customers with sales transactions accurately and efficiently, including cash, check, card and layaway payment

## **SKILLS SUMMARY**

- Friendly customer service
- Latte art and milk steaming
- Customer service experience in busy cafe and restaurant
- Teamwork and strong communication ability
- Detail-oriented and efficient worker
- Fast and willing learner
- Experienced in cafe operations.

### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

Certificate IV in Information Technology [Programming] TAFE 30 Jan 2023 – 6 Dec 2023 English for Academic Purposes Navitas English 30 Oct 2022- 21 Jan 2023 Bachelor's 4<sup>th</sup> Degree in Sustainability Hosei University in Tokyo 2019-Current